fitness.com 2008-12-17

# Fitness.com - Free Exercises, Fitness Equipment, Customized Workout, Fitness Programs, Fitness Articles, Beauty Fitness, Weight Loss, Weight Training, Diet Plans

At Fitness.com, we are very concerned about protecting your privacy. We only gather information about you in order to personalize the experience. We have detailed below exactly what we track and how we use that information, but our basic rule and guiding principle is this:

You are OUR customer. The information you give to us stays with US. We do not give out your information on our site, nor do we give any personally identifying information to our advertisers or partners. Which means even your e-mail address stays a secret between you and Fitness.com.

What We Track? How We Use It?

Anonymous visitors: You can browse Fitness.com without entering any personal information and therefore remain anonymous during your visit. Fitness.com logs IP addresses, browser types, referring sites and page hits but we do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous. We do this for systems administration purposes and these logs will be analyzed to constantly improve the value of the materials available on the web site.

Registered users: We hope that all of our visitors will register with us so that they can use some of the personalization features of the site. Our registration form asks users for name, e-mail address, preferences, and various types of optional demographic information. We use this information to identify you for personalized services on the site, e.g. a personalized cookbook of stored recipes and shopping list. We personalize your Fitness.com experience by using your recipe ratings and saved cookbook to shape our recommendations about the recipes and other information that might be of interest to you. We share aggregate demographic information with our advertisers and partners so that they know the type of people they are reaching on the Fitness.com site, but this information is anonymous, i.e. we do not share your e-mail address or otherwise identify you specifically in that data.

When you send a recipe to a friend on our site, we never disclose that e-mail address to advertisers or partners, but we may use that address to send them a one-time e-mail message of other information about Fitness.com.

Posting information: There are places on the site where you can post, e.g. a recipe, commenting on a recipe, in bulletin boards, etc. We allow this ability only for registered users so that we can hold people responsible for their postings or verify changes as necessary. We are not responsible for what you post, but will operate in good faith and in as timely a manner as possible to correct or withdraw information as deemed appropriate in our Terms of Service Agreement. Please review it.

Premium Membership: When a user decides to become a Premium Member of our site we will ask for billing information. This information will only be used to bill the customer for the service. This information will in no way be used for marketing purposes by Fitness.com, nor will it be shared with any third parties, including our partners.

Cookies: Our site uses cookies to remember passwords for you so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit Fitness.com. We also use cookies to provide our visitors with a tailored user experience that will be of more interest to you. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies, which will simply mean you must login to Fitness.com every time you want to use the personalization features.

Updating your information or opt-out of newsletter: If you would like to correct and/or update your registration information, please use the My Account page.

Links: Fitness.com contains links to other Web sites. Please be aware that our privacy policy does not apply to these linked sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any Web site.

Sharing the information we gather with others: Fitness.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may provide aggregate statistics about our users, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. Fitness.com may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our service agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Fitness.com, our users or others.

Third party advertising: We use Gorilla Nation, Tribal Fusion, Burst Media, Google AdSense and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (never your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Please click here for more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

Third party cookies: In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser to accomplish the above service.

Your consent: By using Fitness.com, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Fitness.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose. We retain the right to change these policies at any time.

Tell us what you think: Fitness.com welcomes your questions and comments about privacy, and what we do, please feel free to e-mail us feedback@Fitness.com or use our comments page.

Thanks for using Fitness.com
